Interviewer: What time do you get up in the morning?
Darius: I usually get up at about seven.
That way I have time to do some exercise or go for a run, or even play squash before breakfast.
Interviewer: What do you have for breakfast?
Darius: Cereal and milk, and toast with honey or jam.
Interviewer: Do you have classes every day?
Darius: I have lectures in the morning every day except Friday.
Lectures are classes for everybody who studies politics. Some of those are online.
Then I also have tutorials on Thursday afternoon and Friday morning.
Tutorials are small face-to-face classes.
Interviewer: And what do you do when you don’t have lectures or tutorials? Is that free time?
Darius: No, I study! I have exams soon.
I work in my room or in the university library.
Interviewer: Where do you have lunch?
Darius: I usually have lunch at uni at about one o’clock, but sometimes I just have a sandwich in a café in town.
Interviewer: Do you go out in the evening during the week?
Darius: Well, music is my main hobby.
I’m in the university choir and I sing every evening from six to seven.
I also play percussion in the university orchestra.
After choir, I sometimes go to the pub with friends, or we watch a film, especially at weekends.
But I often need to study in the evenings, too.
Interviewer: Where do you have dinner?
Darius: Sometimes I go out with my friends, but usually I eat at uni.
The food is quite good, actually. A lot of my friends cook, but I’m terrible at cooking.
Interviewer: What time do you go to bed?
Darius: At about eleven. I’m usually so tired I go to sleep straight away.
It’s my last year, so all I really do these days is study, eat, and sleep.
Interviewer: Do your parents come and visit you?
Darius: My mother comes about once or twice a term.
But I prefer to go home and see her there because I’m terribly untidy,
so when she comes to visit, I need to spend the whole day cleaning and tidying my room!